East Rutherford, NJ 07073

□+1 (551) 206-0263 | ■ anthonyfreay@gmail.com | ♠ www.anthonyfreay.com | □ anthonyfreay | manthonyfreay

Summary _

A software engineer who uses curiosity and drive to solve problems and improve technical skills. Recent internship experiences at BNY Mellon has given exposure to how an application is designed, developed, and deployed within a wide-scale enterprise environment, as well as the importance of Test-Driven Development. Always ready to learn new technologies and continually grow by pursuing technical and non-technical challenges.

Education _

Villanova University (VU)

May 2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN <u>COMPUTER SCIENCE</u> & BACHELOR OF ARTS IN <u>PSYCHOLOGY</u>

Villanova, PA

Awards: O'Toole Presidential Scholar

Current Courses: Software Studio, Mobile App Development

Completed Courses: Data Structures & Algorithms I & II, Platform-Based Computing, Computer Systems I & II, Discrete Structures, Analysis of Algorithms, Theory of Computation, Information Visualization, Database Systems,

Software Engineering, Organization of Programming Languages, & Senior Projects

Skills

Intermediate: Java, Golang, HTML/CSS/JS, Selenium Web Driver **Programming**

Novice: ReactJS, OpenAPI Spec (Swagger)

Deployments Novice: Docker, Artifactory **Databases** Novice: MongoDB, MySQL Languages English (native), Spanish (fluent)

Work Experience _____

BNY Mellon Jun. 2019 - Aug. 2019

New York, NY SUMMER TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

• Overview: Develop and deploy an automated regression test of an API user interface leveraging Java and Selenium Web Driver

BNY Mellon Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

SUMMER TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

Jersey City, NJ

- Overview: Given freedom to fully design, develop, and deploy a full-stack URL shortening service using Golang, ReactJS, MongoDB, Nginx, and Docker company-wide, reaching 35 countries and 52,000 employees
- Front-end: Developed with a minimal design using ReactJS
- Back-end: RESTful API developed using Golang, visually documented using Swagger, and utilized MongoDB to store mapped URLs

Leadership _____

Villanova University Tech Crew (VUTC)

Aug. 2017 - Present

SENOIR STAFF MEMBER

Villanova, PA

- · Assist in the facilitation of VU's event production needs and on-boarding new members
- In the 2018-19 academic year, produced 31 events including Orientation, Special Olympics, and Commencement

Projects .

simple-url Redesigning and optimizing URL shortening service

personal-site

Designed, developed, and deployed personal-site to improve web development skills, increase digital presence,

& improve personal branding

Sideline

Photography Run & manage a freelance photography business specializing in live music, portraits, and streetscapes